Christmas at Graceland is a tv movie, family,
romance film directed by Eric Close.
Laurel, a Chicago-based business executive, travels to Memphis to
secure one of the city's oldest family-owned banks.
While in Memphis, Laurel reunites with old flame Clay, a
local music promoter with loftier aspirations.
Though Laurel tries to keep her eye on the prize of the business acquisition, Clay is very persuasive
reminding her of the days when they were a performing duo on the brink of stardom.
Now Laurel's focus turns to the home of the Blues
and dreams of making music again.
Laurel Couper, played by Kellie Pickler.
Clay Sheppard, played by Wes Brown.
Hatcher, played by Ned Vaughn.
Kathy Nelson, played by Rhoda Griffis.
Antoinette, played by Sara Antonio.
Sally, played by Tamara Austin.
Graceland is a mansion on a 13.8-acre (5.6-hectare) estate in Memphis, Tennessee,
United States, which American singer Elvis Presley once owned.
He is buried there, as are his parents Vernon and Gladys, paternal
grandmother Minnie Mae, grandson Benjamin, and daughter Lisa Marie.
Graceland is located at 3764 Elvis Presley Boulevard (a segment of U.S.
Route 51) in the Whitehaven neighborhood, about nine miles (14 kilometres) south of central
Memphis and fewer than four miles (6.4 km) north of the Mississippi border.
It  was opened to the public as a house museum on June 7, 1982,
and attracts more than 650,000 visitors annually.
Graceland was listed in the National Register of Historic Places on November 7, 1991,
becoming the first site recognized for significance related to rock music.
It was declared a National Historic Landmark on March
27, 2006, also a first for such a site.
Elvis' father, Vernon, inherited Graceland after
Elvis' death on August 16, 1977.
Lisa Marie Presley inherited Graceland after she turned 25 years old.
Following Lisa Marie's death on January 12, 2023, her eldest
daughter, Riley Keough, became the sole trustee and owner.
The film explores themes of holiday, ex-lover, family
holiday, second chance, christmas.
The tone is emotional.